<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>r studio on Landscape Ecology</title>
    <link>/tags/r-studio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in r studio on Landscape Ecology</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/r-studio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Landscape Metrics</title>
      <link>/post/landscape-metrics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/landscape-metrics/</guid>
      <description>This page was created to provide an additional option to quantify landscape configuration using R. The landscape subject to analysis is powerful and can represent any spatial phenomenon. R will quantify, sample, show, and the areal extent and spatial configuration of patches within a landscape. We will cover a few important steps for data analysis and visualization. Firstly, an introduction to how to use the package, the functions it has, and how to extract the information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading files and basic syntax</title>
      <link>/post/software-installationa/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/software-installationa/</guid>
      <description>Reading filesThere are several options to read a file containing your data not only numerical as R can read text, book pages, among others for different analysis. Similarly, your data does not need to be in an excel file, you are able to import a lot of formats as long as you are using the right package. Similarly, it can be directly obtained from other online data sources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software installation</title>
      <link>/post/software-installation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/software-installation/</guid>
      <description>R is an open source software, one of the leaders in its field. Learning R is learning programimg and all the carrer benefits you can get from having some experience with the program. If you are new to R then you will need to install a few things before being able to run landscapemetrics. This will be required only once.
RFirst, we need to install R follow the link and then select your system.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
